Okay now let's take a look at the Amazon bedrock pricing from their pricing page so you can just
go and search Amazon bedrock pricing and you will land at this page. Okay so if I just scroll down
and you can see there are some service tiers so that will be discussing a different lecture
but if it keeps growing down you can see the badge here and it says Amazon bedrock offer
select foundation model from leading a providers like entropic meta,
Mistral and Amazon for batch inference at a 50% lower price compared to on-demand inference pricing.
Okay now if I continue to scroll down and here you will be able to see the model pricing details.
So the first one we have is the on-demand pricing and you can just select the model you want
pricing for so you can just click and the first one is A821 Labs so you can select the region
here wherever it is available and then you can see the pricing. So please remember the pricing is
per 1000 input tokens. So let's say if you select this model then the pricing for 1000 input
tokens is $0.002 and that is for the input tokens and when the model generates a response those
are output tokens. So for every 1000 output tokens this is going to be the price or cost of using
that model. Okay then if I just continue to scroll down you can see for some of the other services
like guardrails, data automation etc the pricing has been provided. Now if I continue to scroll down
and let's just take a look at an example so here are some pricing examples. Now let's take a look
at this entropic pricing. So for the on-demand pricing it says an application developer makes the
following API request to Amazon bedrock in this particular region request entropics cloud model
to summarize an input so it has given an input of 11,000 tokens and then as a summarization of that
the output that has been generated is 4,000 tokens. So let's see how much cost will be incurred
for on-demand pricing. So total cost incurred so input was 11,000 tokens and the pricing is for
every 1000 tokens. So what it has done is 11k tokens divided by 1000 because each API request is
1000 tokens and then it has multiplied it by 0.008. So that's probably the cost per 1000 token.
So if I just scroll up maybe this is an old example but if you see the price so here is the price
per 1000 input token. So it's coming to around 0.0036 but maybe it's an old example so that's what
it has done. So now this is the cost for the input token. Now if I take the cost for output token
so now there are 4,000 output tokens that have been generated by the model. So it has divided
4k tokens by 1000 and per 1000 output token cost is 0. newcomer so that's what it has
multiplied by and that's how it has got the on-demand pricing. So now let's take a look at the
provision throughput pricing. So we are an application developer who buys one model unit of
entropic cloud instant in US West region. So we had discussed earlier for provision throughput
pricing you have to make an commitment of one to six months and you have to select the number
of units you want and in this case he has taken one model unit and for one unit model the costing is
about 39.60 dollars per hour. So one model unit into per hour price for the model unit into 24 hours
so that's one day and you have to make a minimal commitment of either one month or six months.
So in this case he has made an assumption of one month so this is the total cost.
So that's how we can calculate the cost for your workloads and determine which is the right strategy
for you. Okay so that's pretty much it from this lecture. I'll see you in the next lecture. Thank